OKAY.
COME ON, AND
NO PEEKING.
OUR EYES ARE CLOSED
AND WE'RE ABOUT
TO CROSS THE STREET--
VERY GOOD.
OKAY... OPEN UP.
WHAT DO YOU WANT
TO SHOW US?
BECAUSE ALL I CAN SEE
IS THIS BITCHIN' VAN!
YEAH. IT'S FOR OUR
CATERING BUSINESS.
OH.
OH, I THINK I KNOW THAT GIRL.
Monica:
ALL RIGHT. UM...
WE'RE NOT GOING TO REALLY
KEEP IT THIS WAY, THOUGH.
NO?
WE'RE GOING TO PAINT
OVER THE SWORD
AND REPLACE IT
WITH A BAGUETTE.
OH.
MMM.
UM, ALSO, WE DON'T KNOW
WHAT TO DO WITH THIS.
( switch clicking )
OH, YEAH.
I DEFINITELY KNOW HER.
♪ SO NO ONE TOLD YOU
LIFE WAS GONNA BE THIS WAY ♪
♪ YOUR JOB'S A JOKE,
YOU'RE BROKE ♪
♪ YOUR LOVE LIFE'S D.O.A. ♪
♪ IT'S LIKE YOU'RE ALWAYS
STUCK IN SECOND GEAR ♪
♪ WHEN IT HASN'T BEEN YOUR DAY ♪
♪ YOUR WEEK, YOUR MONTH,
OR EVEN YOUR YEAR ♪
♪ BUT I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ WHEN THE RAIN
STARTS TO POUR ♪
♪ I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ LIKE I'VE BEEN THERE BEFORE ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOU'RE THERE
FOR ME, TOO. ♪
REMEMBER THAT GUY
FROM COOKING SCHOOL
I TOLD YOU ABOUT THAT
PUT CILANTRO IN EVERYTHING?
OH, SURE.
"CILANTRO" LARRY.
YEAH. WELL, I'M GOING
TO FILL IN FOR HIM
AS FOOD CRITIC
FOR THE CHELSEA REPORTER.
WOW! MONICA,
WHAT AN AMAZING OPPORTUNITY
TO INFLUENCE...
DOZENS OF PEOPLE.
Phoebe:
HOW COULD YOU
HAVE SAID YES?
WHAT ABOUT
OUR CATERING BUSINESS?
OH, NO, NO.
IT'S JUST ONE NIGHT A WEEK.
PLUS, I GET TO TAKE
ALL OF YOU OUT
FOR A LOT OF
FREE DINNERS.
HEY.
OH, WELL, IN THAT CASE...
THAT WAS ME HOPPING ON BOARD.
OH.
HEY, GUYS.
HEY, ROSS,
QUICK QUESTION FOR YOU.
ARE YOU READY TO PARTY?
I DON'T KNOW. I COULD MAYBE
GO OUT FOR A COUPLE OF BEERS,
BUT THERE'S THIS THING
ABOUT BUMBLEBEES
ON THE DISCOVERY CHANNEL...
NO, NO, NO.
I DON'T THINK YOU HEARD ME.
ARE YOU READY... TO PARTY?
NO!
GANDALF?!
GANDALF IS
COMING TO TOWN?
KATHY'S WITH
HER PARENTS.
I HAVE NOTHING TO DO.
TOMORROW, WE ARE
PARTYING WITH GANDALF, DUDE!
DUDE, WE ARE
SO GOING TO PARTY.
YEAH!
WOW! OKAY. DUDE ALERT.
AND WHO IS THIS GUY?
MIKE "GANDALF"
GANDERSON.
ONLY, LIKE, THE FUNNEST
GUY IN THE WORLD.
I'M GOING TO CALL
AND GET OFF WORK TOMORROW.
AFTER YOU!
THIS IS GOING
TO BE SO COOL, DUDE.
WE NEVER PARTY ANYMORE.
OOOOOOH!
WERE YOU GUYS SMOKING SOMETHING
IN THE BACK OF OUR VAN?
REALLY. WHAT DO YOU MEAN,
WE NEVER HAVE FUN ANYMORE?
YOU HAVE FUN WITH ME.
REMEMBER THE TIME
WE SAW THOSE STRIPPERS
AND YOU PAID ME 50 BUCKS
TO EAT THAT BOOK?
JOEY, YOU
ARE GOING TO
LOVE THIS GUY.
GANDALF IS, LIKE,
THE PARTY WIZARD.
WHY DO YOU
CALL HIM GANDALF?
GANDALF THE WIZARD.
HELLO. DIDN'T YOU READ
LORD OF THE RINGS
IN HIGH SCHOOL?
NO, I HAD SEX
IN HIGH SCHOOL.
OH, UH... JOANNA?
I WAS WONDERING
IF I COULD
ASK YOU SOMETHING.
THERE'S AN OPENING
FOR AN ASSISTANT BUYER
IN JUNIOR MISS...
THAT WOULD BE
A STEP DOWN FOR ME.
NO, ACTUALLY,
I MEANT FOR ME.
THE HIRING COMMITTEE IS
MEETING PEOPLE ALL DAY.
OH. WELL,
I WISH I COULD SAY NO
BUT I GUESS YOU CAN'T STAY
MY ASSISTANT FOREVER.
NEITHER CAN YOU, SOPHIE,
BUT FOR DIFFERENT REASONS.
I'M SO GLAD YOU DON'T
HAVE A PROBLEM WITH THIS
OR I WOULDN'T HAVE
CONSIDERED APPLYING.
REALLY? IN THAT CASE...
THAT'S WHY I'M SO GLAD
THERE'S NO PROBLEM.
IT'S FINE. ACTUALLY,
I'M ON THE HIRING COMMITTEE
SO THERE'LL BE AT LEAST
ONE FRIENDLY FACE.
OH, THAT'S GREAT.
JUNIOR MISS
IS WHERE I STARTED.
REALLY?
HAD TO SLEEP WITH
THE UGLIEST GUY
TO GET THAT JOB.
OH... REALLY?
NO!
YEAH.
I MEAN, NO, NO,
NO, NO, NO, NO.
DON'T YOU WORRY. I'M SURE
WITH YOUR QUALIFICATIONS,
YOU WON'T NEED TO SLEEP
WITH SOME GUY TO GET THE JOB.
ALTHOUGH I MIGHT NEED
SOME CONVINCING.
WELL, UM...
KIDDING!
( both laughing )
GOD, I FEEL WILD TODAY!
OH, MAN,
I AM SO EXCITED
I MAY VOMIT.
WILL YOU CALM DOWN?
HE'S JUST A HUMAN GUY.
YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND.
GANDALF IS AMAZING.
YOU NEVER KNOW
WHAT WILL END UP HAPPENING.
YOU GO OUT FOR A COUPLE OF BEERS
AND END UP ON A FISHING BOAT
TO NOVA SCOTIA.
REALLY?
OH, YEAH. IT'S BEAUTIFUL COUNTRY
UP THERE.
HEY! OKAY, I GOT MY PASSPORT,
FRESH SOCKS,
AND A SNAKEBITE KIT.
IT'S NOT GOING
TO BE EXACTLY LIKE LAST TIME.
ALL RIGHT
I'LL SEE YOU GUYS.
WHOA, WHOA.
WHOA, WHOA,
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA.
I HAVE AN AUDITION.
I'LL HOOK UP WITH YOU LATER.
WHERE WILL YOU BE
AROUND NOON?
SOMEWHERE MAYBE
ALONG THE EQUATOR.
( both laughing )
OKAY.
( phone rings )
HELLO.
IT'S GANDALF!
OOOOOOH!
SO, YOU IN TOWN?
OH, WELL...
WELL, MAYBE NEXT TIME THEN.
WHAT HAPPENED?
HE'S NOT GOING TO MAKE IT.
HE'S STUCK IN CHICAGO.
OH, MAN!
CHICAGO'S SO LUCKY.
STUPID, USELESS
CANADIAN MONEY!
YOU HAVE A VERY
IMPRESSIVE RESUME, MS. GREEN.
I ESPECIALLY LIKE
WHAT I SEE HERE
ABOUT IMPLEMENTING
A NEW FILING SYSTEM.
THANK YOU.
FILING SYSTEM?
YOU MEAN
THOSE LITTLE
COLORED LABELS
YOU PUT ON
ALL THE FOLDERS?
IT BRIGHTENED UP THE INSIDE
OF THE FILING CABINETS.
WELL, THEY, UH... THEY...
THEY DID MORE THAN THAT.
I NOTICE THAT
YOU'VE BEEN ENTRUSTED
WITH A LOT OF RATHER
IMPORTANT RESPONSIBILITIES.
YES. JOANNA REALLY HAS BEEN
AN INCREDIBLE MENTOR TO ME.
RACHEL HAS
BEEN INCREDIBLE
AT GETTING
MY MORNING
BAGEL FOR ME.
IT'S AMAZING HOW
SHE GETS IT RIGHT
ALMOST EVERY TIME.
I... I... OF COURSE...
I HAVE MORE RESPONSIBILITIES
THAN THAT.
OF COURSE.
WELL, THERE'S
THE COFFEE, TOO.
RACHEL CAN CARRY
TWO THINGS AT ONCE.
THAT'S... THAT'S VERY GOOD.
NOW...
A, UH...
BIG PART OF THIS JOB
IS CULTIVATING
PERSONAL RELATIONSHIPS,
ESPECIALLY WITH DESIGNERS.
YES, I REALIZE THAT.
RACHEL SHOULDN'T
HAVE ANY PROBLEM.
HER ONLY PROBLEM
MIGHT BE GETTING
TOO FRIENDLY, IF
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
I LOVE WORKING WITH DESIGNERS.
WITH THEM, UNDER THEM.
WHAT'S THE
DIFFERENCE,
HEY, RACH?
HEY, MY FIRST REVIEW IS OUT.
OH! OH,
THE CHELSEA REPORTER.
OH, THESE USED
TO KEEP ME SO WARM.
RIGHT. LOOK,
I'M ON THE BACK PAGE.
OH! OKAY.
"WOULD I GO BACK
TO ALESSANDRO'S?
"SURE. BUT I'D HAVE
TO ORDER TWO MEALS--
"ONE FOR ME
AND ONE FOR THE GUY
POINTING THE GUN
TO MY HEAD."
WOW! YOU REALLY
LAID INTO THIS PLACE.
THEY DON'T PAY ME
A PENNY A WORD TO MAKE FRIENDS.
I GOT TO GO.
I FOUND A GUY
WHO CAN FIX UP
THE VAN FOR CATERING.
OH, DO YOU WANT ME TO GO
WITH YOU?
NO, NO, IT'S OKAY.
BUT ARE WE SURE
WE DON'T WANT THE WATERBED?
HAVEN'T WE MADE THIS DECISION?
YEAH. ALL RIGHT.
BYE.
( intercom buzzes )
WHO IS IT?
It's Alessandro,
from Alessandro's.
OH, MY GOD.
I want to talk to you
about your review.
OH, MY GOD. OH, MY GOD.
CALL ME ON THE PHONE.
What, so you can hang up on me?
LOOK. I'M NEVER GOING
TO LET YOU UP
SO YOU MAY AS WELL JUST GO AWAY.
Give me a chance to...
Phoebe:
You need to get in? Here you go.
NO, PHOEBE!
Oh, hey, Monica.
I WANT A RETRACTION.
OUR FOOD IS NOT
INEDIBLE SWILL!
I COULDN'T EAT IT.
I HAVE FIVE FRIENDS
WHO COULDN'T EAT IT
AND ONE OF THEM EATS BOOKS.
WELL, OUR SERVICE IS
NOT GROSSLY INCOMPETENT.
THE WAITER CARRIED
THE BREADSTICKS IN HIS PANTS.
WELL... YOU SAID THAT
WE ACCEPT THE DISCOVER CARD
WHICH WE DO NOT.
ALL RIGHT. THAT I'LL RETRACT,
BUT I STAND BY MY REVIEW.
I KNOW FOOD, AND THAT WASN'T IT.
YOUR MARINARA SAUCE
TASTES LIKE TOMATO JUICE.
YOU SHOULD SERVE IT WITH VODKA
AND A PIECE OF CELERY.
I'M PROUD OF THAT SAUCE.
IT'S DELICIOUS.
OH, MY GOD!
YOU OWN AN ITALIAN RESTAURANT
AND YOU THINK THAT TASTES GOOD?
WHERE ARE YOU EVEN FROM?
LEBANON.
HAND ME THOSE TOMATOES.
I'M GOING TO SHOW YOU
WHAT IT SHOULD TASTE LIKE.
COME ON.
HAND THEM TO ME.
HOW LONG IS THIS GOING
TO TAKE, BECAUSE I GOT
ANOTHER CRITIC
I GOT TO GO YELL AT.
( clears throat ):
UH, JOANNA?
I WANT TO TALK
ABOUT THAT INTERVIEW.
I THOUGHT IT WENT VERY WELL.
NO, IT DIDN'T.
THAT'S WHAT I WANT
TO TALK TO YOU ABOUT.
NOW, JUST TO BRIEF YOU...
I MAY CRY
BUT THEY ARE NOT
TEARS OF SADNESS
OR OF ANGER
BUT JUST OF ME HAVING
THIS DISCUSSION WITH YOU.
RACHEL, PLEASE.
DON'T MAKE A SCENE.
THERE'S NOBODY HERE.
SOPHIE, GET IN HERE!
YOU SEE? YOU'RE MAKING
SOPHIE UNCOMFORTABLE.
SHE'S NOT MAKING ME
UNCOMFORTABLE.
CONGRATULATIONS. YOU CROSSED THE
LINE INTO COMPLETELY USELESS.
GET OUT.
DO YOU WANT ME TO QUIT?
WHAT?
WHAT WOULD MAKE YOU THINK THAT?
WELL, ALL OF THOSE THINGS
THAT YOU SAID IN THE INTERVIEW.
IF YOU BELIEVE ANY OF THEM
I MUST NOT BE
A VERY GOOD ASSISTANT.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I AM JUST GOING
TO PACK UP MY DESK...
( rattling drawer )
AND I WILL BE GONE
BY THE END OF THE DAY.
WELL, I GUESS
THERE'S NO USE
ME STICKING AROUND
TILL THE END OF THE DAY.
ALL RIGHT.
WAIT, WAIT, WAIT, WAIT.
YOU CAN PUT
YOUR SAD, LITTLE MUFFIN
BACK IN ITS DRAWER.
IF YOU MUST KNOW
THE TRUTH,
I DIDN'T WANT TO LOSE
A PERFECTLY GOOD ASSISTANT.
WHAT?
THAT'S WHY I SAID
ALL THOSE THINGS
ABOUT YOUR FLIRTING
AND YOUR DRINKING.
MY DRINKING?
OH. I MUST HAVE SAID THAT
AFTER YOU LEFT.
SAID WHAT, EXACTLY?
YOU ENJOY THE OCCASIONAL
DRINK...ING BINGE.
( gasps )
OH, MY GOD!
OH! THAT IS IT!
I AM LEAVING!
YOU ARE JUST
A HORRIBLE PERSON.
NO, WAIT, WAIT,
WAIT, WAIT, WAIT.
IF YOU'RE GOING TO GET
ALL SENSITIVE ABOUT IT.
I DON'T WANT
TO LOSE YOU.
WHAT IF I CREATE
A POSITION FOR YOU?
I'LL MAKE YOU ASSISTANT BUYER
IN THIS DEPARTMENT.
SAY MORE THINGS
LIKE THAT.
UM...
YOU CAN HAVE
YOUR OWN OFFICE
AND A RAISE,
EFFECTIVE TOMORROW.
I'D NEED
AN EXPENSE ACCOUNT.
DONE.
AND AN ASSISTANT.
SOPHIE, GET IN HERE.
However, it seems
like a lifetime, doesn't it?
Starting when Stefano
used Kristin...
HEY. WHAT ARE
YOU GUYS DOING HERE?
I THOUGHT YOU'D BE OUT
PARTYING WITH GAN...DORF.
IT'S GANDALF
AND HE'S NOT COMING.
SO YOU BEEN SITTING
AROUND ALL MORNING?
NO.
I BALANCED
MY CHECKBOOK.
YEAH, AND I GAVE
FIRST NAMES
TO ALL
THE FOOSBALL PLAYERS.
I CAN'T BELIEVE HE DIDN'T COME.
SO WHAT IF HE DIDN'T COME?
WE CAN GO OUT
AND PARTY OURSELVES.
OH, NO.
YOU KNOW,
WITH GANDALF,
WE'D BE OUT ALL NIGHT.
YEAH. WE'D MEET... WE'D MEET
TOTAL STRANGERS
AND HANG OUT WITH THEM.
WELL, WE COULD DO THAT.
( sadly ):
THERE WAS OTHER
STUFF, TOO.
WE'LL DO IT
ALL, AND BETTER.
LOOK, AFTER TONIGHT
GANDALF WILL WANT
TO PARTY WITH US, DUDE.
COME ON!
YEAH!
YEAH! IT'S NOT LIKE
WE DON'T KNOW HOW TO PARTY.
YEAH! ALL RIGHT!
LET'S GO!
MAYBE WE COULD END UP
ON A BOAT AGAIN?
YEAH!
WELL, ALL RIGHT!
HEY, HEY, HEY.
WHEN, UH...
WHEN WERE WE ON A BOAT?
REMEMBER
THAT REALLY COLD MORNING
WHEN YOU WOKE UP AND THOSE DOGS
WERE LICKING YOUR FACE?
YEAH.
THOSE WERE SEALS, MAN.
HEY, LITTLE
QUESTION FOR YOU,
HOW DO YOU THINK
THIS SUIT WOULD LOOK
ON AN ASSISTANT...?
THE OWNER OF ALESSANDRO'S
CAME OVER TO YELL AT ME
BUT I MADE HIM SOME SAUCE,
AND HE OFFERED ME THE JOB
AS HEAD CHEF.
OH, MY GOD! YOU JUST RUINED
THE THING IS WAS PRACTICING
THE WHOLE WAY HOME
BUT I'M SO HAPPY!
I KNOW! CAN YOU BELIEVE IT?
I FINALLY
GET TO RUN MY OWN KITCHEN.
OH, YOU'VE WAITED SO LONG.
AW...
HEY.
HEY, PHEEBS,
QUICK QUESTION FOR YOU:
HOW DO YOU THINK
THIS SUIT WOULD LOOK
ON AN ASSISTANT BUYER
AT BLOOMINGDALE'S?
I DON'T KNOW.
IT WOULD TOTALLY DEPEND
ON HER COLORING, AND...
YOU GOT THE JOB!
YOU GOT THE JOB?!
WHY DIDN'T YOU TELL ME?
OH, IT'S
GOING TO BE SO GREAT!
I'M GOING TO GET
TO HELP DECIDE WHAT WE SELL
AND I'M GOING TO HAVE AN OFFICE
WITH WALLS AND EVERYTHING.
I'M GOING TO HAVE WALLS!
OKAY. IS THIS
THE DAY OF GOOD NEWS OR WHAT?
I GOT US A JOB--
THE WEDDING RECEPTION.
( chuckles )
OH! UM...
PHOEBE, I KIND OF NEED
TO TALK TO YOU ABOUT THAT.
( clears throat )
UM... WELL, I-I-I THINK
IT MIGHT BE TIME FOR ME
TO TAKE A STEP BACK
FROM THE CATERING.
BUT WE'VE ONLY HAD ONE JOB.
I KNOW, BUT NOW
WE HAVE THIS SECOND ONE
AND IT JUST... IT FEELS LIKE
IT'S SNOWBALLING, YOU KNOW?
YEAH. WHAT ARE YOU SAYING?
I GOT OFFERED THE HEAD CHEF JOB
AT ALESSANDRO'S.
WHAT?
IT'S OKAY.
IF YOU THINK ABOUT IT
YOU DON'T REALLY NEED ME
FOR THE BUSINESS.
YOU'RE THE COOK!
WITHOUT YOU, IT'S JUST ME
DRIVING UP TO PEOPLE'S HOUSES
WITH EMPTY TRAYS
AND ASKING FOR MONEY.
ALL RIGHT, BUT, UM...
WELL, I'LL-I'LL PAY YOU BACK
ALL THE MONEY YOU INVESTED
AND YOU CAN KEEP THE VAN.
FOR WHAT?
I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS.
I GOT TO GET OUT
OF HERE.
OH, PHOEBE, WAIT A MINUTE.
I'M AN ASSISTANT BUYER!
WE'LL GET A LITTLE COFFEE
GET ENERGIZED,
AND WE'LL HEAD BACK OUT.
YEAH. ALL RIGHT.
OKAY.
SO, WE'RE
HAVING FUN, RIGHT?
WE DON'T NEED THAT WIZARD GUY.
WE HIT A COUPLE OF CLUBS,
TALKED TO SOME STRANGERS
AND AFTER THIS
WE'LL GO DOWN TO THE DOCKS
AND SEE ABOUT THAT BOAT THING.
I'M KIND OF BEAT.
ACTUALLY...
ME, TOO.
ARE YOU SERIOUS?
YEAH.
THANK GOD. I'M EXHAUSTED.
( sighing )
SO, YOU GUYS
WANT COFFEES?
YEAH, BUT I DON'T WANT
TO BE UP TOO LATE
SO I'LL HAVE A DECAF.
YEAH. ME, TOO.
ACTUALLY, COULD I GET
SOME HOT WATER
WITH A LITTLE LEMON?
I THINK I STRAINED MY VOICE
SCREAMING IN THERE.
DOES IT HAVE TO BE
SO LOUD?
OH, I CAN'T HEAR
A WORD YOU'RE SAYING
MY EARS
ARE RINGING SO BAD.
I'M JUST GLAD
I BROUGHT
THAT EXTRA PAIR
OF SOCKS, YOU KNOW?
I USED THEM AS MITTENS.
I DIDN'T
WANT TO TOUCH A THING
IN THAT LAST PLACE.
HOW SAD ARE WE?
YEAH. I KNOW.
YOU KNOW WHAT? WE'RE NOT SAD.
WE'RE NOT SAD.
WE'RE JUST NOT 21 ANYMORE,
YOU KNOW?
I'M 29 YEARS OLD, DAMN IT
AND I WANT TO SIT
IN A COMFORTABLE CHAIR
AND WATCH TELEVISION
AND GO TO SLEEP
AT A REASONABLE HOUR.
YEAH.
YEAH, AND I LIKE
TO HANG OUT
IN A QUIET PLACE
WHERE I CAN TALK
TO MY FRIENDS.
YEAH.
AND SO WHAT
IF I LIKE TO GO HOME
THROW ON SOME KENNY G
AND TAKE A BATH?
WE'RE 29, WE'RE NOT WOMEN.
OH, THERE YOU ARE.
OKAY. I'M-I'M GLAD
THAT YOU DECIDED
TO HEAR ME OUT.
OKAY. I'M HEARING.
OKAY. I'VE BEEN
DOING A LOT OF
THINKING-- A LOT--
AND, WELL, I CAME UP WITH
A WHOLE BUNCH OF BUSINESSES
THAT YOU CAN DO
WITH YOUR VAN.
OKAY. UM... YOU COULD BE
A FLOWER DELIVERY PERSON.
WHAT?
OR...
A BAKERY DELIVERY PERSON?
( stammering )
PIZZA?
MONICA!
ALL RIGHT. I'VE GOT A WHOLE
BUNCH OF STUFF IN THIS AREA
BUT I'M GETTING
THE FEELING
THAT YOU DON'T
WANT TO DELIVER.
NO.
OKAY.
AND I'M GUESSING IF YOU
DON'T WANT TO DELIVER
YOU PROBABLY DON'T WANT
TO PICK UP STUFF, EITHER.
NO.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
LET'S DO THE CATERING BUSINESS.
REALLY? ARE YOU SURE?
YEAH. YOU KNOW, I-I...
I MADE A COMMITMENT
TO YOU, AND...
YOU KNOW, IT'D-IT'D BE FUN.
OH, IT WILL BE FUN!
OH, YAY!
OKAY. LET'S PLAN
THE WEDDING RECEPTION.
OKAY.
( giggles )
WOW.
YOU REALLY WANTED ME
TO DO SOMETHING
WITH THIS VAN.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I WANT YOU
TO TAKE THE CHEF JOB.
REALLY?
YEAH.
THAT'S WHAT
YOU REALLY WANT.
YEAH. I DON'T WANT TO BE
THE REASON YOU'RE UNHAPPY.
THAT WOULD JUST
MAKE ME UNHAPPY
AND I REALLY DON'T WANT TO BE
THE REASON I'M UNHAPPY.
THANK YOU.
BESIDES, IT MIGHT
BE KIND OF FUN
TO FORM THE NEW A-TEAM.
Rachel:
OH, HI, MRS. LYNCH.
IS JOANNA IN ALREADY?
OH, MY GOODNESS.
YOU HAVEN'T HEARD.
HEARD WHAT?
JOANNA...
PASSED AWAY LAST NIGHT.
OH, MY GOD! HOW?
WELL, SHE WAS LEAVING WORK,
AND SHE WAS HIT BY A CAB.
OH, MY GOD!
OH, I CANNOT BELIEVE IT.
OH, I KNOW.
OH, GOD. OH, GOD...
OH, GOD.
I DIDN'T REALIZE
THAT YOU WERE SO CLOSE.
YES... SO CLOSE.
MRS. LYNCH, I KNOW THAT
THIS IS AN EMOTIONAL
AND DIFFICULT TIME
FOR ALL OF US...
BUT BY ANY CHANCE DID JOANNA
SEND ANY PAPERWORK YOUR WAY
BEFORE... IT HAPPENED?
NO, NOTHING.
IMAGINE...
IF SHE'D JUST
STEPPED OFF THAT CURB
A FEW SECONDS LATER.
OH, YES, YES.
JUST A FEW SECONDS AND
SHE'D STILL BE WITH US.
NOTHING ABOUT AN
ASSISTANT BUYER OR...?
I'M SORRY.
I HAVE TO GO.
( weeping )
( cheerfully ):
GOOD MORNING.
OH, SOPHIE, I GUESS
YOU DIDN'T HEAR ABOUT JOANNA.
I SURE DID.
I'M SO EXCITED
ABOUT HAVING MONICA
COME ON BOARD WITH US
ALTHOUGH I DO FEEL BAD
ABOUT HAVING FIRED CHEF EMILIO.
IT IS LIKE LOSING
A MEMBER OF THE FAMILY.
OF COURSE, THAT
LITERALLY IS THE CASE
FOR SEVERAL OF YOU.
TONY, CARLOS, MARIE,
PLEASE, TELL YOUR FATHER
HOW MUCH
WE'RE GOING TO MISS HIM.
NOW, I KNOW
THAT MONICA
HAS A LOT OF GREAT IDEAS
FOR THIS PLACE--
WELL, YOU ALL
READ THE REVIEW--
SO, WITHOUT MUCH
FURTHER ADO,
I PRESENT TO YOU
OUR NEW HEAD CHEF.
UM, I JUST WANT TO SAY, UH,
THAT WITH A PINCH OF EXCITEMENT
A DASH OF HARD WORK
AND A DOLLOP OF COOPERATION
WE CAN HAVE THE RECIPE...
ARE YOU GOING TO KILL ME?